searchforvideo.com 2010-05-28

# Searchforvideo - Privacy Statement Searchforvideo

Searchforvideo respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use searchforvideo's services ("searchforvideo Services"). Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission or as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").

## Cookies

Upon your first visit to searchforvideo.com, searchforvideo may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. Searchforvideo uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. Searchforvideo will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the searchforvideo Services may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

## What Information Do We Collect?

Searchforvideo does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.

## Links to Other Sites

The videos displayed and/or linked to by the searchforvideo Service are developed by people over whom searchforvideo exercises no control. Other links are also on sites not controlled by searchforvideo. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. searchforvideo encourages you to read the privacy policy of all web sites you visit. Searchforvideo may choose to exhibit its results in the form of a "URL redirector." When searchforvideo uses a URL redirector, if you click on a URL on a searchforvideo page, information about the click is sent to searchforvideo, and searchforvideo in turn sends you to the site you clicked on. Searchforvideo uses this URL information to understand and improve its service.

## With Whom Does searchforvideo Share Information?

Searchforvideo may share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, we may disclose how frequently the average searchforvideo user visits searchforvideo, or which searchforvideo pages are most often used. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

## Third Party Advertising

Searchforvideo uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

## Third-Party Web Beacons

We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://ondemand.indextools.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=stats.indextools.com).

## Google Advertising Cookie

We use third-party advertising companies such as Google to serve ads when you visit our website. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy

By using the searchforvideo Services and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy. Searchforvideo may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
